VIKTORIA BELLAK, MA

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER SCRUM MASTER

Contact Details:

***** +43 123456

⊠ viktoria.bellak@hotmail.com

Skills:

- Design Thinking
- UX Design
- · Scrum, SAFe, KANBAN
- · Time Boxing, Sprint Planning, Pl Planning
- Self-organization
- · Trainer for agile training
- · Employee and customer support
- · Practiced teamwork skills
- · High flexibility and versatility
- Conducting competitive Analysis
- Defining Business Requirements & User
 Stories
- User research with Interviews, Affinity
 Mapping and Card sorting
- Defining User Personas, User Journeys & User Flows
- · Creating Sitemaps
- · Creating Navigation & Design Patterns
- Prototyping
- · Conducting Usability & Preference Testing
- Organizing and Dealing with Feedback
- Applying UI Design to Prototypes using Material Design Guidelines
- · Creating Design Language System(s)
- · End-2-End Design

Tools:

- · JIRA, JIRA Hive
- · Figma, Sketch
- Adobe Illustrator
- · Marvel
- · Draw.io
- · Visual Studio, Lyssna, Sublime
- · Miro
- N-Design, Photoshop, Photoscape
- · Videopad

Languages:

- · German (Mother Tongue)
- · English (C2)
- · Spanish (B1)

Profile:

With my education as UX Designer and experience as (SAFe)Scrum Master, I can help to build the right products and achieve the right goals. My passion for designing and coorporating to create delightful user experiences keeps me motivated to stay ahead of any new challenges along the way.

Experience:

2022 – 2024 Maternity Leave / Educational Leave

Training for UX Design @CareerFoundry

2016 – 2022 Project Manager / Scrum Master

T-Systems Austria GesmbH

Working on various projects (Waterfall as well as Agile)

2013 – 2016 Marketing and Quality Management
DHL Express Austria

Education:

2023-2024 UX Designer, CareerFoundry

· 2020-2021 Digital Enabler (Incubator), RWTH Business School

2020 SAFe Scrum Master 5.0

2018 Certified Project Management Associate

2017-2019 Master of Arts in Business

FH BFI Wien, Project Management and Organisation

2013-2016 Bachelor of Arts in Business, FH Wien der WKW,

Entrepreneurship (Bilingual)

2008-2013 Vienna Business School, Mödling, Plus-Klasse